We're wrapping up two incredible days at
AI Native DevCon London.
>> It's our second [music] in-person event
and it's even bigger and better than
last time.
>> A big welcome to AI Native Dev London
2026.
>> [music]
>> Honestly, the atmosphere has been
[music] incredible. We've had some
amazing sessions from people from
OpenAI, Anthropic, Meta.
>> We had a lot of fun. I loved [music] the
event's talk, poking fun a little bit at
artificial intelligence. And
>> [music]
>> more importantly, we had an incredible,
incredible hallway track.
>> It's been great to connect and to learn
from a bunch of you here and see how
you're using AI day-to-day. [music]
>> The caliber of conversations and
insights and learnings was super, super
high. I personally have had
conversations [music] with practitioners
and leaders that taught me a lot. And
I'm going [music] back home with a lot
to digest and think about how to apply
it.
>> [music]
>> Best part is we get to do this all again
in November, November 3rd and 4th
[music] in New York. So, please come
along. It'll be great to compare notes
and see how far we've [music] come in
just 5 months' time.
>> It's going to be amazing and I hope to
see many [music] of you there.